nice Covey's you see if I can put you
somewhere nice there we go oh let me
take off let me take off this matter
this sweater is not calm a I merchandise
but this t-shirt is definitely common
and I merchandise you guys know where
you can buy them call me AI slash shop
and now I can say that I'm about I got a
slash shop let's see if that works I
love that link oh yeah comma dot AI
slash shop just like Logan Paul my cops
last shot we can now say that so there's
no new product right now you guys gotta
wait nine minutes
it is 251 if I had a large cloth I would
be showing that to you but they were all
out of large clocks at the large clock
store so that's uh no it's true I went
there and they were out they were trying
to sell me alarm clocks not large clocks
and they were trying to sell me phones
that had clock apps on them and I just
it was too much so we had to leave the
pawn shop did have some nice watches but
large box no we're not gonna talk about
large box we're here to talk about the
new product but just like The Bachelor
when they give away the final rose you
guys are gonna have to wait tick tick
tick tick tick when will you be able to
see your gold star minutes couple weeks
couple weeks we got we got big things
coming you know big things that's right
I'm so I actually have one in the new
product right here it's clacking on the
table a little bit yeah that Flavor Flav
clock you know what time it is this
right um no I actually one of the new
products right here this is the noisy
mix and you when you tap the new product
against the table um can I say
just going live yeah they're excited
there's a lot of there's 100 let's see
the three of them no no I don't think
they can see the boy let's go please
what up Skokie's what's going on here
you didn't show them the new product
you're just tapping no I was just
tapping the product using intact no yeah
just tapping it's not a do we on we will
tell you that well yeah and of course
I'm surprised nobody's found it yet when
you win it it's already live I'm
surprised nobody's famished
well it loads so nice I know right and
the font that's right I'm surprised I
even mentioned it in the periscope nice
picture changes y'all the picture
changes right nice oh it's solid autumn
you seen the best thing we haven't
believe I thought was 200 just dropped
to 90 no no don't be crazy
alright guys um you were looking is it a
projector wall clock no no no no no no
no it's not that
we're live on periscope Ricardo ready
for the new product announcement all
right guys there's a little teaser
before the new product if you guys
haven't seen it I gotta hide the product
hey it's the new website you might think
it looks like the old website but it's
new is it a job offer for Chase no
flexor a panda it's not a flex rependa
let's let's go through some of this we
wrote some copy today ah yes the future
of driving his open-source look at
phones for years every phone
manufacturer shipped a crappy operating
system they were so bad they didn't even
have names motorola razr OS LG phone
firmware some tried to do better with DB
LS on blackberry and Symbian OS on Nokia
spoiler alert those companies went out
of business then the game changed in
2007 Apple released the iPhone it wasn't
immediate you had the phone needs a
physical keyboard haters and those who
couldn't believe that it only had two G
and no apps only the web but they didn't
really matter slowly it became to define
what a phone was here is what our story
begins here's where our story begins
in 2015 I was approached by a friend to
the vision system for the Tesla Model S
perhaps as Paul Graham would say the
iPhone of cars after a miscommunication
with Elon Musk the contract fell through
but the future was obvious every
pathetic car manufacturer writing low
quality autonomy features this is phones
in 2007 sure BlackBerry's and GM's look
nice but after a few OTA updates from
Tesla they will be a joke what happened
to phone will happen to cars the iOS and
the Android the autopilot and the open
pilot common AI is building the Android
for cars we have an open-source driving
agent that runs on Honda Toyota and GM
and we have hundreds of active users
uploading the data back to us so the
system it gets better updates are pushed
out and we slowly move forward in five
years the world will call it obvious
of course cars will play out like phones
test the world on autopilot one idiot
will still be trying to run when
phone and everybody else will be running
the open-source operating system from
comma a I this is coming eyes open pilot
we have almost 8,000 stars now on github
we're gonna make this readme look
beautiful we support Honda's Acuras
Toyota's Lexus GM how can you add
support for your car easy it's open
source I went on up to the new product
yeah it's coming in a little bit 3 p.m.
guys 3 p.m. she can work with us this is
why comma AI to be honest our interviews
are brutal if you can get hired here you
can get hired anywhere you'll work
harder than anywhere else you'll get
paid less and you won't have a team to
blend into so why come nai because you
want to do something with your life you
want to see progress being made you want
to change the way the narrative will
play out you are bored and want the
world to be less boring and at the end
of the day you want to win so we have a
legitimate open positions page local
cook we're using lever I paid these
assholes lots of money I'm sorry they're
not a valuable partner valuable partner
lots of money so we could have no job
listings apply apply for positions that
coming I will throw it out if you just
want to email give give me a job
becoming AI that's good too I'm looking
at positions they're all engineers in
the role in San Francisco so if you're
an engineer in San Francisco we're gonna
win you want to join the winning team or
you want to join that you know well you
know we won't we won't we've set it off
terrible things
thank you thank you I did not design it
myself you can you can compliment our
design our designer did a great job with
this stuff the positions button is
broken these are broken seem to work for
me okay guys two minutes two three two
minutes to the new product oh yes and of
course the new shop build your kid
beautiful retrofit your car with the
copilot oh yeah yawns are gonna be
shipping out flipped if you buy any on
now it's gonna come flip you can add
your panda right in here you can add
your giraffe right here we're not gonna
click that drop down for another two
minutes um yeah pretty beautiful guys
it's pretty beautiful why the oneplus
are blue are they do order one of these
right now so yeah you can check out the
new shop here Aeons pandas giraffes
pause maze t-shirts debug boards and
comma powers is the quality low I think
the quality should be pretty high right
now yeah I know about I know about that
let's see if the quality tile is going
periscope right here Steve's on the high
quality this eating stream no no no it's
not a eating stream okay guys I know
what time it is it's one minute to three
that's the noise it makes
oh if you guys the websites already live
at kamidana yo bro bro the sales they're
coming in loving these sales look at
that number go up we just sold four
hundred and two dollars where's the
stuff I wonder if anyone's bought
yeah shop back home at REI is old bro
here it is the new product 3 p.m. we got
to do it on unveiling and on sale give
the network card box oh yeah it's behind
this box it's behind this box ready to
knit after this commercial break
this commercial is brought to you by the
comma panel the column peddle is not a
new product it's been around for a long
time and you can build your own kamma
pedal thank you for watching the coma
pedal commercial now 3:00 p.m. new
product reveal it's going it's going
it's the Honda bust your ass oh yeah
check it out it's the latest in giraffe
technology it has screws 1 2 3 using
active components aka a diode it's been
reduced from four switches down to two
switches only two switches even you can
remember what they do this one toggles
the camera power this one toggles the
forwarding or something like that
there's only two of them though so it's
twice as easy to remember as for this is
a Honda Bosch giraffe
check out this connector I am sorry for
the color but this is printed on a form
to printer this is the highest quality
3d printed connector UV cured and it's
yours for the same low price of $60 this
is compatible with the Honda Civic
hatchback the 2017 plus Honda CRV and of
course the 2018 plus Honda Accord Honda
Accord if you'll take three you can go
right now to shop.com ADATA yo sorry
comedy I'd slash shop don't get it
twisted don't go to the right shop I'm
sorry there's two we're gonna fix that
up later today
Amazon bro driving assistant will
be replaced by self-driving cars that's
right with a
update your driving a system will be nah
we don't say that
bro common AI slash shop that's right by
an official comma Bosch giraffe today at
comedy I slashed shop the unofficial
come AI bashed your apps unfortunately
will cease working because they flipped
around can one and cam - they should
flip that back um we want to put the
radar on can one you don't have a Bosch
Honda then you don't need a Bosch mama
giraffe but if you want to buy three oh
there is a downside though there is a
downside the downside is that they don't
ship for two to eight weeks they won't
ship for two to eight weeks but I'm
two-day weeks you'll be getting your
very own Honda Bosch graph we are
setting it go guys any miles sake right
okay
so nice for only $60 you can plug your
comma power right in here you'll be able
to plug all future compatibilities stuff
into here this is the new product it is
a Honda Bosch giraffe this is a panda
it's not a new product but you can buy
these on
tamo dollar i slash shop as well this is
a panda but this is a Honda Bosch draft
check out the new website if you know
anyone who are aggressive now about
higher and you have lots and lots of
money this is a pedal from a Toyota what
are you gonna plug into the Ethernet
port well one thing you can plug for is
your homemade , pedal it is Ethernet zon
both sides don't plug it into a computer
though cuz the computer will blow up
you want the new what's the new Leon
you see how it's done no this is a
normally on is it feeling you can have
this Elin you can buy it today the new
Leon we are shipping the Aeons flipped
and I think we're finally doing a
shipper plus re-release so we'll be
updating shipper plus new Aeon you've
got it Geo haha comms do you have back
on still off I don't know I'm loving
these sails and love them by Bosch dress
right now bye bye bye aren't the new
cars stop and go you wouldn't why else
do you need this Ethernet port it's a
secret but don't worry your giraffes our
future compatible if you buy a giraffe
today it'll work in the future that's
right
future compatible um yes Bob man ways
yeah you don't want those to limit error
use RJ 12-month it only has less pins
dude yeah so buy your Honda Bosch draft
today it comes with two switches two
switches instead of four it's doubly
easy to remember this is a Toyota
giraffe it's not as good-looking as the
brand new Honda ba strap but if you have
a Toyota don't buy our Honda bus traffic
even though it's better looking you're
gonna have a bad time
oh man three people are checking out
right now Cree people are purchased I
got the live Shopify analytics right up
here bye bye bye what is this junk no
junk
oh yeah we're also gonna put the
ethernet cover in all the Honda Bosch
giraffes that we ship on to bust your
ass high quality stop it has three
screws that's you know it's quality this
has zero screws I shouldn't talk bad
about our other products great they're
all great all products are great
it has a lot of screws this is the stair
controller from with Toyota oh yeah this
is an active miles counter just go to
bed accommodate oh yeah you can see that
there so do we have any questions about
the Honda baath drift new open pilot is
great
what is it I didn't say that did I
explain the product oh well let's see
what it says on the website because I
don't really know what it does
I'm the social media guy let's read the
website
cars have many can buses not exposed on
the main obd2 connector giraffe like
this new one that we just announced even
the social media guy can put two and two
together
it's an adapter board that gets you in
so basically the new one here is the
Honda Bosch look that picture is the
same as this we have them in real life
it's not just main Photoshop like zukes
yeah so what does it do it design it
would tell you what cars design format
really doesn't do a very good job of
functionality it passes through the
signals to the existing driver
assistance system or turn the switches
off remember this one they told me this
in the press briefing it has half as
many switches so it's doubly easy to use
it's like unplugging but better that
makes sense
what proxy the signals through your
panda which you can also buy my way come
a nice nice shopping only $90 are great
um you guys should buy them they're
great they're the universal car
interface they have give your car USB
port which you can connect to your Aeon
the EON look cool it turns on wow that's
a quality eel shop tech house I had me
comment adding a slash shop you could
shop that cons I think it's actually the
old trunk we did not date again oh man
I'm loving all the purchases right now
Oh where'd we get the connector file
from I don't know man who stole of him
somewhere probably now I can be scanned
him good it's gang under something a
half as many twice as easy inversely
proportionate that's right it might even
be nonlinear maybe even ee is easy cuz
can you really remember for if something
you can kind of remember two or
something
look we're watching me on periscope it
also has a neo compatible fake Ethernet
port Ethernet that port with access to
can one can to start to detect 12 volts
and ground so make sure you guys check
out our shop
right now oh we have a news site where
you can read our medium posts medium
posts our Twitter's right here make sure
to follow us on Twitter oh alright with
way mo on to metrics we compete with way
mo we want to have more miles driven
than we mo and we want to have more
Twitter followers than window right now
way Mo's beating us at both of them but
not proportional to the amount of money
they've spent so way most spent billions
we've spent millions so this off by like
a factor of a thousand yeah I think
comma guys the thousand acts cheaper
than away mo and we have almost as many
Twitter followers and half as Ben's mom
we have half as many models and a little
over half as many Twitter followers
that's a great deal every comma a I
dollar is worth like 500 way more
dollars that's interesting to think
about
alright guys but this is this is the
come AI Bach giraffe available for sale
right now at comedy I slash shop this is
a Toyota giraffe also available if you
have a Toyota at comma dollar i slash
shop oh this is a cop Hetal you can't
buy these anywhere they're ultra rare
baby blue exclusive wire splitter
followers an important metric because
you gotta have metrics and they have to
be important it's important to have
metrics because twitter twitter is great
we love twitter um this is a comma a
panda it comes in a but a box i don't
have the box but i promise if you buy a
panda it comes in a box or your money
back
yeah yeah panna is nice right it's nice
look at has a USB port
these white pandas have Wi-Fi there's
gray pandas
we're being shipped to anybody Oh laughs
oh yes it comes look laughs yes Anna's
coming the cutest little panda boxes
that's got our logo on it right there oh
yeah look at that this doesn't look like
when you open it up gray pandas are kind
of where it's at though you can buy a
gray panda for only $1.99 it comes with
a $55 GPS antenna um super high quality
high-precision GPS product Maps you
overworking a wobble right now we're
getting the wobble down oh man I'm gonna
keep shilling as long as the sales keep
going up we got we got tons of sales
right now there's there's 27 visitors at
our shop right now which is crazy
there's so many visitors go to our shop
let she'll let she'll check at channel
check out the new shop htps
laughs shop that's right make sure that
link works oh yeah
Wow our are really ended yeah I'm just
showing on uh none slack right now for
the stop if you guys aren't on our slack
go to slacked off Tommy I make sure to
get on that slack we have over 3,500
people now that's so many slack ease if
you want to ask involve questions how
are what GPU is going yeah of course I
saw Blake's map back response you know
we love partners and we work with people
that's a lie we don't because people
will always let you down but you know it
won't let you down Honda Bosch giraffe
you could buy one for only $60 on come
to the I slash shop you go right now you
buy the product just buy just a $60 man
this is like as much as like a nice
dinner and not only last night you know
what lasts probably about like two years
until it's obsolete
a come AI Honda bhaskar app make sure to
buy one right now why should you buy one
from your Toyota no it won't work with
your Toyota it only works with with with
Honda Bosch know if firfer yeah I know
we gotta remove that copy a a yellow a
yeah many things we gotta do your
giraffe hasn't let you down see I like
that look we got a guy in here shilling
for the product a real user testimonial
if you want to come give a testimonial
about your Honda Bosch track have you
used on the boss tracks yeah what did
you think is amazing oh there we go we
have it right here
giraffes are incredible and amazing
people are watching this off the ropes
don't don't don't don't let them know
but this is the life combined two
screens right now what's going on
yourself boys no that's so we check the
quality because have been low guys do
you know what our number two cars on
open pilot we didn't know we know but we
looked recently why don't we have a team
page we do have a team page go to jobs
we have the jobs
I saw his quality page we'll link to it
right now that call me daddy I slash
jobs build the future let's let's look
at it let's look at it
by my car oh yeah you look at a job that
matters you'll have me reality that's
what everybody's looking for we're
selling you meaning in your life come on
you two
why see because where do you think the
future is over there
Wow I mean I'm not gonna hang up yet
there's 104 people on this still
watching I don't know what else can I
show for this is a comedy bug yeah check
out the condom debug it has a great
panda in it oh great panda perfect what
is our business plan to win you know
other people don't really want to win
I've heard we got some bleep documents
they don't want to win we want to win no
that's the business then six people will
win that's never happening but yep for
those just joining us this is the Honda
boss draft you can buy an accommodating
I slash shop this is a common panda this
is a collar panda right here this is an
old Panda and a grape and Betina coming
ID bug which is also available at
Comikaze I slash shop
what's top card open it's the Honda
Civic go to the news page here yeah you
can read all our medium posts there's
water prototype this Honda bas you have
no way man this is a product for sale I
know it has a c2 connector but that's by
design you want the highest quality of
Sidra
printed out a form - yeah see look at
this guy regretting not purchasing 128
gig option make sure when you guys buy
your Eon
you could choose right here everybody in
life makes choices you could choose this
64 gig or the hunt 28 gig midnight black
with midnight black heatsink and
midnight black cables the second most
popular car is the underperforming laggy
Toyota Prius no motorcycles
no midnight black for the win by a
midnight black if I had a minute I'd
like to show you right now I would but I
don't think I have one I've a normally
on though
here's Neil thank you for joining this
periscope where we presented the Bach
giraffe only by the most expensive do
that's the way to do life man that's the
way to do life we'll just make the comma
a I Eon expensive edition it's just more
expensive number of people running open
pilot hundreds hundreds of people run
open pilot you wouldn't believe it's
only hundreds by the amount of data that
we're dealing with at comma a I we have
huge data the data is super massive big
try stream labs yeah yeah yeah well
think about it
all right bros thank you for joining
this product announcement it's been
great to have you here
more than 5-hundred overall less than
five hundred weekly it's been great
spending some time with you we'll be
spending a lot more time together in the
future we have a lot more announcements
coming
but for now get your Honda Bosch giraffe
right now a comment on the ice last shop
thank you for joining